A Guide to the Arthur M. Squires Papers, 1888-1987 (Bulk 1940-1986)
Special Collections, Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University
- A Series, Subject Files, 1888-1985, n.d.
  - Box A-19, 1946-1984, n.d. (Box 19)
    - Hydrogen Sulfide, Scrubbing at Appleby-Frodingham, 1958.
    - Hydrogen Sulfide, Scrubbing, Hot Low-BTU Gas, 1976.
  - Box A-20, 1925-1981, n.d. (Box 20)
    - Hydrogen Sulfide Scrubbers, Tri-Potassium Phosphate Plant, 1949.
    - Hydrogen Sulfide Scrubbers, Tri-Potassium Phosphate Plant, 1950.
    - Hydrogen Manufacturing, Carbon Monoxide Shift Scrubbers, 1956.
    - Hydrogen Manufacturing, Low Temperature Condensing, 1958.
    - Hydrogen Manufacturing, General Information, 1930-1974.
    - Hydrogen Manufacturing, Reforming, 1955-1962.
    - Hydrogen Manufacturing, Shift Reactions, 1967-1972.
    - Hydrogen Manufacturing, Partial Oxidation of Gases, 1949-1952.
    - Hydrogen Manufacturing, Partial Oxidation of Gases, 1948.
    - Hydrogen Manufacturing, Partial Oxidation/Coal, 1959.
    - Hydrogen Manufacturing, Partial Oxidation/General Information, 1955-1959.
    - Hydrogen Manufacturing, 1953-1962 Partial Oxidation/Oil 1953-1962.
    - Hydrogen Manufacturing, Steam-Iron Process, 1961-1967.
    - Hydrogen Synthesis, 1948-1979.
    - Hydrogen Synthesis, 1958-1984.
    - Hydrogen Synthesis, Brownsville Reactor, 1951-1980.
    - Hydrogen Synthesis, Brownsville Reactor, 1953-1981.
    - Hydrogen Synthesis, South African Coal, Oil & Gas Corporation Limited (SASOL), n.d.-1982.
    - Inert Atmospheres, 1962.
    - Iron, Blast Furnaces, 1961-1973.
    - Iron, Blast Furnaces, 1962-1969.
    - Iron, Blast Furnaces, 1940-1967.
    - Iron, Blast Furnaces, 1925-1967.
    - Iron, General Information, 1933-1958.
    - Box A-30, 1961-1978. (Box 30)
      - Sulfates, Southern Pines, NC, Workshop, 1978.
      - Sulfates, Research Programs, 1973-1976.
      - Sulfates, Research Programs, 1971-1977.
      - Sulfates, Research Programs, 1974-1977.
      - Sulfates, Legislation and Standards (See also other file in Box A-29), 1976-1977.
      - Sulfates, Miscellaneous Reports and Articles, 1964-1978.
      - Sulfate Acceptors, 1961-1977.
      - Sulfate Acceptors, Ruth (AMS' Notation); Michael Somer Paper, 1971.
      - Sulfates, Conoco Report 7/1/73-1/31/76, 1977.
      - Sulfide Ore Metallurgy, 1970-1971.
      - Sulfur Dioxide Acceptors, 1973-1974.
      - Sulfur Dioxide Control, 1961, 1977.
      - Sulfur Dioxide Control, 1972-1974.
      - Sulfur Dioxide Control, 1971-1976.
      - Sulfur Dioxide Control, Battelle Memorial Institute Reports, 1966-1967.
      - Sulfur Dioxide Control, Battelle Memorial Institute Reports, 1968-1969.
      - Sulfur Dioxide Control, 1969-1975.
      - Sulfur Dioxide Control, 1969-1980.
  - Box A-21, 1946-1973, n.d. (Box 21)
    - Iron, General Information, 1947-1949.
    - Iron, LD Process, 1958-1972.
    - Iron, Open Hearth Process, 1959-1962.
    - Iron Ore, Concentration of, 1946-1969.
    - Iron Ore, Sinter Machines, 1948-1970.
    - Iron Ore, Reduction of (Arthur D. Little, Inc.), 1949-1957, n.d.
    - Iron Ore, Reduction, Armco Steel, 1957.
    - Iron Ore, Reduction, Carbon Deposits, 1955-1959.
    - Iron Ore, Reduction, Carbon Deposits, 1957.
    - Iron Ore, Reduction, Direct Melting, 1957-1964.
    - Iron Ore, Reduction, Fluid Bed Pilot Plant, 1957.
    - Iron Ore, Reduction, Fluid Bed Pilot Plant, 1957.
    - Iron Ore, Reduction, Fluid Bed Pilot Plant, 1954, 1957.
    - Iron Ore, Reduction, Evian Conference, 1967.
    - Iron Ore, Reduction, Evian Conference, 1967.
    - Iron Ore, Reduction, General Information, 1948-1973.
    - Iron Ore, Reduction, General Information, 1951-1966.
    - Iron Ore, Reduction, General Information, 1948, 1955.
    - Iron Ore, Reduction, H-Iron Development, 1958-1967.
    - Iron Ore, Reduction, H-Iron Development, 1955-1957.
    - Iron Ore, Reduction, H-Iron Pilot Plant, 1955-1959.
  - Box A-22, 1926-1976, n.d. (Box 22)
    - Iron Ore Reduction (Red), HyL Process, 1958-1959.
    - Iron Ore Red, Kinetics, 1946-1958.
    - Iron Ore Red, Kinetics, 1953-1961.
    - Iron Ore Red, Kinetics, 1926-1966.
    - Iron Ore Red, Krupp Renn Process, 1947, 1958.
    - Iron Ore Red, Madaras Process, 1946-1962.
    - Iron Ore Red, Passivation of H-Iron, 1958.
    - Iron Ore Red, R-N Process, 1957-1958.
    - Iron Ore Red, Stelling Process, 1946-1958.
    - Iron Ore Red, U. S. Steel, 1955-1968.
    - Iron Ore Red, WEL-Iron Process, 1958-1959.
    - Iron Ore Red, Wiberg-Soderfors Process, 1948-1955.
    - Iron Scrap, 1970, 1974.
    - Iron Slag, 1942-1973.
    - Iron/Steel, D-LM Process Report, 1967.
    - Iron/Steel, 1959-1970.
    - Iron/Steel, L-D Process, 1969-1973.
    - Iron, Technical Data, 1950-1956, n.d.
    - Kinetics, 1967-1972.
    - Lead, 1970.
    - Lime, 1964-1967, n.d.
    - Limits of Growth, 1970.
    - Liquid-Liquid Extraction, 1953-1963.
    - Liquefied Natural Gas (LNG), 1973-1974.
    - Low Temperature, Helium, 1961-1963.
    - Low Temperature, Hydrogen, 1956-1961.
    - Low Temperature, Liquid Hydrogen, 1950-1963.
    - Low Temperature, Liquid Methane, 1946-1972.
    - Low Temperature Refrigeration, 1952-1967.
    - Lubrication, 1976.
    - Magnesium Chloride, 1964-1967.
    - Manuscript, Talk in Moscow, 1976.
  - Box A-24, 1948-1981, n.d. (Box 24)
    - Natural Gas Production, by Nuclear Stimulation, 1971, 1973.
    - Net Energy.
    - Nitrogen Oxide Control, 1970-1973.
    - Nitrogen Oxide Control, 1958-1974.
    - Noise Pollution, 1965-1972.
    - Nuclear Power, 1963-1980.
    - Nuclear Power, 1963-1979.
    - Nuclear Power Costs, 1967.
    - Nuclear vs Coal Study, ChE191 (Course Number), 1967.
    - Nuclear Energy Centers, Squires Heading, "Nuplex", 1966-1971.
    - Ocean 1970.
    - Ocean, Thermal Aspects of, 1974-1976.
    - Odor Control, 1955-1978.
    - Oil Desulfurization, 1964, 1967.
    - Oil Desulfurization, 1961-1975.
    - Oil Gasification, Synthetic Gas Plants, 1959-1972.
    - Oil Hydrogenation, Articles, Correspondence, 1948-1969.
    - Oil Hydrogenation, Further Correspondence and Articles, 1957-1972.
    - Oil: Partial Oxygenation, 1964, 1966.
    - Oil Resources, 1980, n.d.
    - Oil: Shale, 1948-1982.
    - Oxygen Manufacturing, 1939-1981.
    - Ozone, 1974.
    - Packed Beds, 1974.
    - Packing, 1962, n.d.
  - Box A-25, 1909-1977, n.d. (Box 25)
    - Loose Surface (LS) Filter, Fuller Reports and Comments on Reports, 1961-1965.
    - LS Filter, After Fuller, n.d.-1973.
    - LS Filter, 1960-1974.
    - LS Filter, Before Fuller (Drawings, Patents), 1919-1974.
    - LS Filter, Before Fuller (Correspondence, Patent), 1926-1961.
    - LS Gas Adsorber, 1960-1968.
    - Panel Bed Filter, Early Work, 1961-1965.
    - Panel Bed Filter, Early Work, 1961-1971.
    - Panel Bed Filter, Early Work, 1961-1962.
    - Panel Bed Filter, Prior Art, 1909-1973.
    - Panel Bed Filter, 1961-1975.
    - Panel Bed Filter, 1967-1975.
    - Panel Bed Filter, 1967-1976.
    - Panel Bed Filter, Adsorber, 1973-1974.
    - Panel Bed Filter, Liquid (Whitmire), 1977.
    - Panel Bed Filter, Rodon, 1976-1977.
    - Panel Bed Filter, Rodon, 1976-1977.
    - Panel Bed Filter, Tall Panel Studies.
    - Panel Bed Filter, Tall Panel Studies, 1975.
    - Panel Bed Filter, Wu.
  - Box A-26, 1948-1978. (Box 26)
    - Paper Manufacturing, 1967-1970.
    - Paper Manufacturing, 1975, 1978.
    - Patent Information, 1954-1972.
    - Patent Information, 1967-1973.
    - Patent Information, 1959-1973.
    - Patents (AMS), Dolomite Reforming, 1948-1968.
    - "Equipressure" Reforming, 1964.
    - Patents, Chemical & Miscellaneous, 1966-1973.
    - Patents, Fuel Desulfurization, 1964-1969.
    - Patents, "G" Seal, 1949-1964.
    - Patents, "G" Seal, 1963.
    - Patents, "G" Septor, 1959-1962.
    - Patents, Gasification, 1966-1977.
    - Patents, Air Skip, 1961-1966.
    - Patents, Various Correspondence, 1961-1964.
    - Patents, Panel Bed/Gas Filter, 1962-1976.
    - Patents, Power Cycle, 1964-1969.
    - Patents, Review of Dolomite Chemistry, 1964.
    - Patents, "Top Heat" Examples, 1964.
    - Patents, "Top Heat" Information, 1964.
    - Patents, "Top Heat" Information, 1964-1965.
  - Box A-27, 1911-1981. (Box 27)
    - Patents, Review of Dolomite Chemistry, 1964.
    - Patents, Demonstration of "Top Heat" Chemistry, 1962.
    - Patents, Trademark, Copyright Information, 1962-1970.
    - Petrochemicals, 1958-1973.
    - Petroleum, 1955-1983.
    - Petroleum/Coke, 1973.
    - Petroleum Refining, 1961-1981.
    - Philadelphia & Reading, 1950-1960.
    - Philadelphia & Reading, 1960.
    - Phosphorous, 1962-1968.
    - Plant Design, 1966-1973.
    - Plant Design, 1967-1971.
    - Pollution, 1966-1974.
    - Pollution Control, 1971-1972.
    - Polymers, 1966, 1969.
    - Population, 1966-1974.
    - Power Cycles, 1958-1963.
    - Power Cycles, 1950-1974.
    - Power Cycles, 1933-1973.
    - Power Cycles, 1955-1968.
    - Power Cycles, 1905-1972.
    - Power Cycles, 1911-1968.
    - Power Cycles, 1954-1974.
  - Box A-28, 1919-1984, n.d. (Box 28)
    - Power Cycles, City College (NY) Flowsheet Studies.
    - Power Cycles, Exotic, 1960-1974.
    - Power Cycles, Field, 1954-1964.
    - Power Cycles, Art (Combined Cycle), 1919-1959.
    - Power Plant Design Report, 1972.
    - Power Plant Siting, 1971-1974.
    - Power Transmission, 1966.
    - Process Metallurgy, 1937-1976.
    - Profitability, 1967.
    - Proposals, 1971-1976.
    - Prospective Instructors, 1970.
    - Protein from Fuel, 1967.
    - Publications, 1958-1959.
    - Pumped Storage, 1968, 1971.
    - Research and Development, Planning and Evaluation, 1964.
    - Recarbonation, 1971, n.d.
    - Reliability, 1969, 1971.
    - Reprint Requests, Letters, 1961-1974.
    - Research Budgets, 1968-1969.
    - Research Budgets, Drafts, 1964-1968.
    - Research Reports, Reports and Drafts, 1963-1970.
    - Research Proposals, 1969-n.d.
    - Research Proposals, 1967-1971.
    - Salt Water Sweetening, (Saline Water Conversion), 1960-1965.
    - Scientific Research Instruments, Proposal, 1967.
    - Secondary Recovery, 1966, n.d.
    - Seminars, 1968-1970.
    - Settling Drums, 1952.
    - Sludge Incineration, 1970-1974.
    - Solar Energy, 1968-1981.
    - Solid Flow, 1970-1971.
    - Solids Handling, 1960-1984.
    - Solids Pumps, 1946-1963.
  - Box A-29, 1895-1980, n.d. (Box 29)
    - Solids Separations, 1971.
    - Solids Transfer, n.d.-1977.
    - Solids Transfer, 1965-1980.
    - Solids Transfer, 1960-1967.
    - Solids Transfer, 1905-1972.
    - Solids Transfer, 1928-1985.
    - Solids Transfer, 1895-1973.
    - Solids Transfer, Dense Phase, 1958-1970.
    - Solid Waste, 1967-1982.
    - Solid Waste, 1965-1974.
    - Solid Waste, 1966-1977.
    - Solid Waste, Gasification 1966-n.d.
    - Solid Waste, Incineration, 1972-1973.
    - Solid Waste, Pyrolysis, 1970-1972.
    - Spray Drying, 1965, 1968.
    - Statistics, 1946-1966.
    - Steam Automobiles, 1976.
    - Substitutes for Natural Gas, 1964-1966.
    - Sulfates, 1973-1980.
    - Sulfates, Stationary; Mobile; Bio, 1971-1979.
    - Sulfates, Regional Studies, 1975-1978.
    - Sulfates, Legislation and Standards, 1970-1977.
  - Box A-31, 1964-1985, n.d. (Box 31)
    - Sulfur Dioxide Control, Dry Scrubbing 1978-1979, n.d.
    - Sulfur Dioxide Control, 1971-1981.
    - Sulfur Dioxide Control, 1969-1977.
    - Sulfur Dioxide Control, 1971-1979.
    - Sulfur Dioxide Control, Lime, Limestone, Dolomite, 1964-1970.
    - Sulfur Dioxide Control, Lime, Limestone, Dolomite; 3rd Limestone Symposium, 1967.
    - Sulfur Dioxide Control, Lime, Limestone, Dolomite, 1967.
    - Sulfur Dioxide Control, Stanford Research Institute Report, 1973.
    - Sulfur Dioxide Control, Oak Ridge National Laboratory Report, 1973.
    - Sulfur Dioxide Control, U. S. Department of Energy Report, 1984.
    - Sulfur Dioxide Control, 1969-1985.
    - Sulfur Dioxide Control, 1967-1974.
    - Sulfur Dioxide Control, 1969-1976.
    - Sulfur Dioxide Control, 1969-1975.
    - Sulfur Dioxide Control, 1964-n.d.
  - Box A-32, 1957, 1976, n.d. (Box 32)
    - Sulfur Dioxide Control, Air Pollution, 1957-1970.
    - Sulfur Dioxide Control, Pollution, 1970-1971.
    - Sulfur Dioxide Control, 1971.
    - Sulfur Dioxide Control, 1968-1970.
    - Sulfur Dioxide Control, 1968.
    - Sulfur Dioxide Control, 1968.
    - Sulfur Dioxide Control, n.d.-1976.
    - Sulfur Dioxide Control, 1971-1973.
    - Sulfur Dioxide Control, 1966-1969.
    - Sulfur Dioxide Control, 1967-1974.
    - Sulfur Dioxide Control, 1963-1970.
    - Sulfur Dioxide Control, Kellogg Processes, n.d.
    - Sulfur Dioxide Control, Lime, 1975.
    - Sulfur Dioxide Control, Consolidated Electric Utility Hearing, 1974.
    - Sulfur Dioxide Control, Lime, 1967-1975.
    - Sulfur Dioxide Control, Lime, 1974.
    - Sulfur Dioxide Control, Lime, 1974-1975.
  - Box A-33, 1926-1981, n.d. (Box 33)
    - Sulfur Dioxide Control, Low Sulfur Fuel Oil, 1966.
    - Sulfur Dioxide Control, Scrubbers, 1972-1975.
    - Sulfur Dioxide Scrubbers, Lime, 1970-n.d.
    - Sulfur, 1926-1969.
    - Sulfur, 1950-1971.
    - Sulfur Production, 1960-1971.
    - Syllabi and Course Notes, n.d.-1981.
    - Talks, n.d.-1960.
    - Tall Stacks, 1961-1975.
    - Tar Sands, 1966-1982.
    - Technical Data, "Top Heat" Cycle, 1964.
    - Technical Data, 1950-1970.
    - Technical Data, 1938-1967.
    - Technical Data, 1939-1972.
    - Technical Data, 1963-1981.
    - Technical Data, 1947-1967.
    - Technical Data, 1947-1967.
    - Technical Data, 1947-1958.
    - Technical Data, 1962-n.d.
  - Box A-34, 1938-1979. (Box 34)
    - Thermal Analysis, 1938-1969.
    - Thermal Analysis, 1963-1976.
    - Thermal Grad(ient?) Power, 1971.
    - Thiophene Scrubbers, 1951.
    - Top Heat, 1965.
    - Total Energy System, 1972.
    - Town Gas, General Information, 1958, 1971.
    - Town Gas, Partial Oxidation of Oil, Oil Quench, 1955-1956.
    - Trips, United Kingdom, 1958.
    - Units, 1969-1971.
    - Unsteady-State Processing, 1967.
    - Vanadium, 1965-1974.
    - Waste Heat, 1967-1980.
    - Waste Heat Utilities, 1972.
    - Water Pollution, 1964-1977.
    - Water Resources, 1964-1976.
    - Wood Gas, 1979.
    - Wood Gas, 1979-1980.
    - Wood Gas, 1965-1985.
    - Zimmerman Process, 1959-1964.
- B Series, Publications, 1946-1986.
  - Box B-1, Publications, 1946-1986. (Box 35)
    - 4 Publications, 1946-1958.
    - 2 Publications, 1961.
    - 1 Publication, 1962.
    - 2 Publications, 1966.
    - 5 Publications, 1967.
    - 6 Publications, 1968.
    - 5 Publications, 1969.
    - 4 Publications, 1970.
    - 7 Publications, 1971.
    - 10 Publications, 1972.
    - 1 Publication, 1972.
    - 8 Publications, 1973.
    - 5 Publications, 1974.
    - 12 Publications, 1975.
    - 4 Publications, 1975.
    - 18 Publications, 1976.
    - 5 Publications, 1977.
    - 10 Publications, 1978.
    - 3 Publications, 1978.
    - 5 Publications, 1979.
    - 2 Publications, 1980.
    - 3 Publications, 1981.
    - 1 Publication, 1982.
    - 5 Publications, 1983.
    - 6 Publications, 1986.
  - Box B-2, Publications, 1972-1983. (Box 36)
    - 20 Volumes, Assorted Proposals/Reports: Coal Energy/Gasification/Liquefaction. 1972-1983.
- C Series, Correspondence Files, 1947-1987, n.d.
  - Box C-1, 1966-1986 n.d. (Box 37)
    - American Association for the Advancement of Science (AAAS), 1966-1986.
    - AAAS, 1969-1986.
    - AAAS, 1976.
    - AAAS Committee on Environmental Alterations, 1970-1974.
    - AAAS Committee on Environmental Alterations, 1970-1972.
    - AAAS Committee on Environmental Alterations, 1968-1971.
    - AAAS Committee on Environmental Alterations, 1968-1971.
    - AAAS Boston Symposium; David Berkowitz, 1969-1974.
    - AAAS Articles, 1971, n.d.
    - AAAS Philadelphia, 1986.
    - AAS Philadelphia, 1985-1986.
    - AAAS "Science," 1976-1986.
    - AAAS "Science," 1967-1976.
    - American Chemical Society (ACS), 1966-1979.
    - ACS, 1961-1975.
  - Box C-2, 1959-1987, n.d. (Box 38)
    - ACS, 1963-1985.
    - Activities, n.d.-1986.
    - Activities, 1980-n.d.
    - Activities, 1982-n.d.
    - A. D. Little Company, 1959-1967.
    - AGA-CTC, 1977.
    - Ahlstrom (Finland), 1984-1985.
    - Ahlstrom (Finland), 1984-1985.
    - American Institute of Chemical Engineers (AIChE), 1966-1978.
    - AIChE Puerto Rico, 1971.
    - Air Products, 1960-1977.
    - Air Products, 1960-1977.
    - Alberta Research Council, 1971-1985.
    - Alberta Research Council, 1971-1985.
    - Allied Chemical Corporation, 1964-1974.
    - Allis Chalmers, 1973.
    - Alpert, Seymour, n.d.-1986.
    - Aluminum Company of American (Alcoa), 1959-1979.
    - Amax Engineering and Management Services Company, 1974.
    - American Academy of Arts and Sciences, 1980.
    - American Coal Enterprises, The "Independence," 1980-1985.
    - American Coal Enterprises, The "Independence," 1980-1981.
    - American Cyanamid, 1950-1965.
    - American Electric Power, 1960-1978.
    - American Geological Institute, 1971.
    - American Heritage of Invention and Technology, 1986-1987.
    - American Independent Oil Company, 1969.
    - American Messer Corporation, 1959-1971.
    - American Oil Company, 1972-1978.
  - Box C-3, 1947-1986, n.d. (Box 39)
    - American Power Conference, 1969-1975.
    - Air Pollution Control Association, 1970-1980.
    - Applied Energy, 1975-1981.
    - Argonne National Laboratory, 1968-1977.
    - Armco Steel Corporation, 1959-1961.
    - Arnold, John (Also See "Air Products"), 1982-1986.
    - American Society of Mechanical Engineers (ASME), 1961-1984.
    - Aston University, 1975-1981.
    - Atomic Energy Commission, 1967-1974.
    - Auburn University, 1980.
    - Australia, 1960-1985.
    - AVCO Corporation, 1968-1978.
    - Avidan, Amos, 1982.
    - Babcock and Wilcox, 1959-1976.
    - Bagnold, R. A., 1955-1982.
    - BAHCO, 1976-n.d.
    - Bailey, E. G., 1949-1961.
    - Barker, J. J., 1960-1962.
    - Bassett, L. G., 1950, 1961.
    - Basu, Prabir, 1981-1986.
    - Battelle Columbus Laboratories, 1971-1983.
    - Battelle Memorial Institute/Other Battelle Facilities, 1959-1977.
    - Bayles, Allison, 1959-1969.
    - British Coal Utilisation Research Assoc., Ltd. (BCURA), 1959-1977.
    - BCURA, 1959-1972.
    - BDM Corporation, 1976-1983.
    - Bechtel, 1964-1974.
    - Benedict, Manson, 1947-1986.
    - Benmol Corporation, 1981.
    - Berg, Charles, 1977.
    - Bergbau-Forschung GMBH, 1968-1978.
    - Bergougnou, M. A., 1970-1985.
  - Box C-4, 1959-1986. (Box 40)
    - Berkeley, University of California at, 1977-1981.
    - Berkeley, 1972-1980.
    - Berkowitz, David (Also See "AAAS"), 1980-1983.
    - Bethlehem Corporation, 1978.
    - Bethlehem Steel Company, 1959-1972.
    - Beyer, G. H., 1975-1977.
    - British Iron and Steel Research Association (BISRA), Ridgion, Maurice, 1957-1974.
    - Bituminous Coal Research, Inc., 1965-1979.
    - Bjorling, G., 1959-1969.
    - Borgstrom, G., 1973-1974.
    - Botterill, J. S. M., 1963-1986.
    - Bradford University (England), 1985-1986.
    - Brazil, 1986-1987.
    - British Gas Corporation (Gas Council), 1970-1974.
    - British Columbia, University of, 1982.
    - Bronowski, J., 1959-1960.
    - Brookhaven National Laboratory, 1962-1975.
    - Brookhaven National Laboratory, 1962-1963.
    - Bucknam and Archer (Attorneys), Hemisphere Publishing Corporation, 1975-1983.
    - Bureau of Mines, 1947-1973.
    - Bureau of Mines, 1970-1975.
    - Bureau of Mines, 1959-1973.
    - Bureau of Mines, Bruceton, Pennsylvania, 1959-1978.
    - Bureau of Mines, Grand Forks, North Dakota, 1960-1970.
    - Bureau of Mines, Morgantown, West Virginia, 1962-1974.
  - Box C-5, 1959-1987, n.d. (Box 41)
    - Bureau of Mines, Salt Lake City, Utah, 1968-1972.
    - Business Cards, n.d.
    - Butler Manufacturing Company, 1960-1977.
    - Calderbank, P. H., 1959-1962.
    - California Institute of Technology (CalTech), 1976-1977.
    - CalTech, 1975-1982.
    - CalTech, 1974-1982.
    - California (State Government), 1978.
    - Cambridge University, Konrad, Kenneth, 1978, 1980.
    - Canada, Dept. of Energy, Mines, Resources, 1956-1981.
    - Canadian Industries, Ltd., 1967-1968.
    - Can-Do, Inc., 1974.
    - Cantata Singers (Historic), 1948-1961.
    - Carbon Conference, 1981.
    - Carnegie Institution of Washington, 1959, 1978.
    - Carnegie Mellon University, 1968-1978.
    - Central Electricity Generating Board (CEGB), Sir Harold Hartley, 1963-1981.
    - Central Research Institute (Japan), 1967-1972.
    - Council on Environmental Quality (CEQ), 1976-1977.
    - CEQ, 1976-1977.
    - Chemistry Education, 1970.
    - Chemical Engineering Department (VPI&SU), 1978-1980.
    - Chemical Engineering Department (VPI&SU), 1979-1987.
    - "Chemical Engineering" Magazine, 1967-1974.
  - Box C-6, 1958-1986. (Box 42)
    - Chemistry Department (VPI&SU), 1976.
    - Chem Systems, Inc., 1976.
    - Chem Systems, Inc., 1975.
    - Chevron, 1972-1985.
    - Chilton, 1970.
    - China, Research Institute of Environmental Chemistry, 1981-1982.
    - China (Taiyuan, Shanxi Province), 1982-1985.
    - China, Joint AIChe-CIESC Meeting, 1982.
    - China, People's Republic of, 1979-1980.
    - China, People's Republic of, 1979-1983.
    - China, People's Republic of, 1979-1986.
    - City College (New York), 1961-1983.
    - City College, 1967-1980.
    - City College, 1964-1978.
    - City College, 1967-1986.
    - City College, 1982-1987.
    - City College, 1966-1979.
    - City University (Washington Office), 1968, 1977.
    - Clark, L. J., 1958-1962.
    - Clean Energy Systems, Inc., 1973-1974.
  - Box C-7, 1960-1985. (Box 43)
    - Clean Fuels Institute (City University of New York), 1978-1981.
    - Coal Combustion Workshop, 1977-1980.
    - Coal Combustion Workshop, 1978-1980.
    - Coal Combustion Workshop, 1977-1979.
    - Coal Combustion Workshop, 1977-1980.
    - Coal Combustion Workshop, 1977.
    - Coal Course Syllabi, 1976-1985.
    - Coal Course Syllabi, 1977-1980.
    - College of Engineering (VPI&SU), 1977-1983.
    - Columbia Gas, 1972.
    - Columbia University, 1973-1980.
    - Combustion Engineering, 1967-1975.
    - Combustion Institute, 1976-1977.
    - Combustion Power Company, Inc., 1970-1979.
    - Combustion Systems, Ltd., 1977.
    - Commonwealth Edison, 1960-1975.
    - Commonwealth Edison, 1971-1973.
    - Commonwealth Edison, Papers by Gordon R. Corey, 1969, 1971.
    - Commonwealth Edison, 1957-1975.
    - Commonwealth Edison, 1969-1975.
    - Commonwealth Edison, 1969-1971.
  - Box C-8, 1958-1986. (Box 44)
    - Commonwealth Edison - Lurgi, 1970-1976.
    - Compacting Coal Fines, Foreman-Squires Process, 1976-1983.
    - Congress, U. S., 1972-1986.
    - Congress, U. S., 1970-1976.
    - Congress, U. S., 1967-1973.
    - Connecticut, University of, 1972-1973.
    - Conservation Center, 1966-1968.
    - Consolidated Edison, 1960-1976.
    - Consolidated Edison, 1968-1975.
    - Consolidated Natural Gas Company, 1959-1976.
    - Consolidation Coal Company, 1959-1962.
    - Consolidation Coal Company, 1966-1977.
    - Consolidation Coal Company, 1966-1976.
    - Constructors John Brown, Ltd., 1958-1960.
    - Constructors John Brown, Ltd., 1960.
    - Continental Can, 1973.
    - Cooper, George, Wooster, Ohio, 1978-1980.
    - Copeland, G. G., 1966.
    - Cornell University, 1971-1986.
    - Corson, G. & W. H., Inc., 1970.
    - Commonwlth Scient. & Indust. Research Org. (CSIRO), Australia, 1967-1982.
    - CSIRO, 1961-1977.
    - Czechoslovakia, 1970-1976.
    - Danial, Cuthbert, 1962-1983.
  - Box C-9, 1958-1987, n.d. (Box 45)
    - Daniel, Cuthbert, 1960-1963.
    - Davidson, Frank, 1985-1986.
    - Davy Powergas, Ltd., 1973.
    - Dearborn, R. J., 1963-1968.
    - Dearborn, R. J., 1963-1967.
    - Dekker, Marcel, Inc., 1982.
    - DEMAG, 1958-1962.
    - Demmy, Richard, 1978.
    - Denmark, 1971-1982.
    - Dent, F. J., 1958-1974.